Uh, our info is limited, these guys aren't in our database.
All we really know is that they came from Guangzhou, China.
I'm still investigating to get the exact details.
How close are we on the server?
I still got, uh, two-thirds or more?
And the shopping mall migration?
Seventy percent. It's 'cause we're only working nights.
We have to avoid any tracking by Babylon.
I have to go get Jian myself.
Those bastards are gonna go after her quickly.
What's that?
I think they already found us.
Can't get a clear shot.
Container's in the way.
As expected.
Hold your positions.
We're going in.
Listen carefully. Put your personal grudge aside.
Jeong Jinman has to be captured alive. Translate.
Jeong Jinman needs to be captured alive, sir.
He has to be alive.
Just don't get in my way.
You'll die first. Translate.
Ah, shit.
Uh what he said was
Ah, die first?
I didn't get the last part.
What?
That one-eyed bastard
Appreciate you working so late.
We can begin now.
A SHOP FOR KILLERS 2
EPISODE 04 RAID
Understood.
I will retrieve the asset and put things back in order.
Who is it?
Who could make the great Kusanagi act so submissively, huh?
I can keep on climbing higher and higher, but there's always another level.
Don't you miss fieldwork?
Not at all.
The smell of blood
And gunpowder just stays in your nose.
Ugh.
I'd rather be a knight than a pawn anyway.
Or even better, I could be the one who designs the board in the first place. :cue
As for capturing Jeong Jinman, you need to be the one to do it.
I like the sound of that.
And Q?
Q will
Get rattled.
I need the one who leads this team to be someone cold.
Hmm
Women's intuition.
Smoke!
Don't panic. Hold your positions.
He's the most skilled agent in your team.
Don't you think it's long overdue for J to lead a unit?
I don't think it's combat skills that determines a good leader.
If the target's Jeong Jinman, I think it does.
That's not it.
I'm talking about Bale.
Bale's just a hunting dog at this point.
If you take him off his leash, he'll find Jinman for us.
We should be using that.
Working with Bale to capture Jinman was actually J's choice as team leader.
You can't keep coddling him forever because he's your little brother.
J has the skills he needs.
Branch Chief
Are you and my brother still seeing each other?
Heavy radio signal detected.
Remove it.
If you really cared about Jun
Why stick him with a time bomb like Bale
And send him after Jeong Jinman?
If you're afraid of things like that,
You're in the wrong line of work entirely.
You should try going back to being yakuza again.
Or open a bar in Dotonbori
And leave the dangerous missions to us. :cue
Hey, Japanese.
-  It's a trap. - What?
If they hid the server in a place like this,
Wouldn't it mean they're prepared to bolt at any moment?
What are you doing?
Translate it.
If they hid the server in a place like this,
Wouldn't it mean they're prepared to bolt at any moment?
That's what he's said.
Bravo, Tango,
Find dead ends of containers
That can be connected to the current Alpha position,
And identify all trucks, cranes, and modes of transportation
Within a 100-meter radius.
Possible ambush on Tango.
J, forget about Tango.
Hey, didn't you say it was a trap?
What are you doing? Translate it.
If it's a trap, we don't go in?
Are you scared?
That's right, the enemy of my enemy should be my friend.
After you.
Grenade!
Marco. Marco!
I'm okay.
I'll be right back.
Jinman's here, that slick fuck.
Bravo, current location?
After you.
It's a trap. :cue
That hurts!
Shit.
Long time, no see.
Jeong Jinman.
I'm just sorry we have to meet like this.
J, don't forget.
We need Jeong Jinman alive.
What the hell's that moron doing?
I told you we have to capture him alive!
I thought I made it clear to you.
If you get in my way, you'll die first.
Shit.
Ugh
Move it.
Shit.
Look! Over there!
Snipers, what are you doing?
Hurry up and stop that truck. Move to ten o'clock now!
We're out of time, let's haul ass!
You always did have something up your sleeve, Jinman.
Always so petty.
:cue
Just ram through it!
Hold on to something!
All these clever little tricks
Are only gonna blow up in your face.
Jeong Jinman, I'll see you in hell--
Tell me,
Are we being recorded in the command center?
No, ma'am.
We don't record unofficial internal operations.
Good work, everybody.
You can all go home.
Q's operation is in a few hours.
What's our angle here?
Hmm
I'll figure something out.
I'm starving.
Can you handle it?
:cue
Can I get room service?
Even though Bale's a psycho, how could he kill his own team like that?
Dying like a dog as soon as you leave Japan
I heard that J was Q's younger brother.
That hurts!
- Yeah? -  Everything is set.
But there are two employees from another department
And the bus driver on board.
I think that
Looks more natural, don't you think?
Whoo!
Good job, K.
You understand?
Jeong Jinman was the one who killed J.
Bale didn't do it.
We have to make sure that Q never discovers the truth
Under any circumstances.
This stays between us.
Fortunately, the residents had all left the island.
Your friend Miss Arin rushed to Seoul because of her uncle's sudden passing.
And it looks like she won't be able to come back.
We'll make it so nothing happened here tonight.
So, as long as you keep quiet, that's the end of it.
You'll be free to return to your normal life.
However,
Once Miss Jian leaves here, you'll be strangers from that moment on.
Any contact is forbidden.
Hey, I don't think that's necess
That's going too far.
Woojin
If you need help, you can contact me at this number.
CO., Ltd. JAEWON CLEANING Team Leader Kim Jaewon
Arin
No.
Your real name is
Jian, isn't it?
I don't think I'll be any help cleaning here.
Let me know when it's all done.
I'll be at the house.
Woojin, wait.
:cue
Do you think it's okay to let him leave, just like that?
There are traces of him having accessed the app data.
When you catch up, what are you gonna say?
That boy Woojin
Do you like him?
Stay level-headed.
You remember Bae Jeongmin, right?
- We don't know who'll come looking and-- -  Unni
I'm really hungry.
Why don't we eat something?
We got some mumallaengi.
Auntie Soonae grows the radishes, dries and seasons them herself.
It's so good.
And these are bangiip muchin and myeolchi that Auntie Pilsun made.
And this one
Auntie Jeomrye, she found out I liked sausage and stir-fried vegetables,
So she made this for me.
Ah
Meongge-jeot
Auntie Jeomrye's specialty.
Jian,
We don't have time to be doing this.
This stuff
I've never
I never got to just be like this with Uncle.
After getting here
Living a normal life like everyone else, it was just really nice.
Having someone there for me
And me being there for them too.
Laughing together,
Making meals,
Just talking
Normal.
A normal life, you know?
Living a normal life like everyone else gets to.
Until yesterday, I really
Really believed I could keep going like this.
Look, your uncle really tried.
He did everything he could for you, Jian.
I know he did. I know that.
I found a way here to live life on my own terms.
It's better than that cage he kept me in 'cause it was dangerous.
And that was his past catching up to us.
It had nothing at all to do with me.
Even still
If you were to stay here, Woojin and everyone around you
Will all be in danger.
I know that.
I'll go back to my uncle, I just
Could we just
Have one moment?
Can we have one more meal as normal people first? :cue
WOOJIN
Team Leader, she isn't alone. How should we handle this?
You can eliminate anyone who gets in your way.
Just get her.
And for our extraction?
We can transport you on our ship.
This is bad.
You have to go now!
Woojin, is there another way to the docks?
On the back side of the island, there's a way there.
Listen carefully.
I'll stay and stall them as long as I can.
Head to the docks with Woojin.
Once you get down there, find the boat called the JW.
Director Kim, give them cover.
Right. I'm on it.
Unni.
I'll be fine.
Listen, your unni will never die.
:cue
They're coming!
Team Leader, there's a four-wheeler headed towards the docks.
It looks like Jeong Jian.
Bravo, start making your way in.
Let's roll out.
Are you all right?
We have to hurry and catch up to Jian.
Woojin!
:cue
Arin, hold on to me!
Arin
Arin, get up.
Jeong Jian
Wait, is that your boat over there?
You can't!
Shit.
This is your last chance.
If you don't come with me, your boyfriend will also die just like that.
Hey, my boat's right there.
:cue
You're her, huh?
So Minhye.
Woojin, hard left now!
Seal it off.
I'm sorry, Woojin.
I'm doing fine.
Look, I'm still in one piece.
So don't worry.
Hey, don't say you forgot,
Do you remember my promise?
In Hanam-do.
I won't let anyone
Touch even a hair on your head.
I won't let them get the chance.
You're right.
They won't have a chance in hell.
:cue
Jian, get down!
Boom.
Give them a warning shot, to wake them up.
Woojin, drop down!
Woojin. Woojin!
It's okay. Just wait a second.
Jeong Jian!
I want Jeong Jian brought in alive.
Jian, hey
Jeong Jian.
That's your name, right?
Jeong Jian?
Uh-huh.
Even your name is beautiful, Jian.
I
Hey, didn't I promise you?
Not a single hair.
Not a single hair on your head.
Let me just say
Thanks for hanging out
With a hick like me.
Woojin, hey!
Don't close your eyes!
No! You can't
You can't
Jeong Jinman!
A SHOP FOR KILLERS 2
BASED ON THE NOVEL BY KANG JI YOUNG